响应式设计！调整你的浏览器，去看哪些网站能自适应
Responsive design, I know. [LAUGH] It's fun to resize your web browser and
而哪些网站会出来落后的水平滚动条，是非常有意思的
see which sites resize gratefully and which sites remain defiantly large with
但是响应式设计并不仅仅只适用于web开发
gross horizontal scroll bars. But responsive design is not just for
如今，手机与平板电脑之间的界限正在消失。
the web. Today, the lines between phones and tablets are disappearing. So
使你的UI在多种多样的屏幕上自适应非常重要
it's important to think about your UI will scale in our multiscreen world.
千万不要被打倒哦！这就像是在为网页设计响应布局一样，
Don't be overwhelmed. Just like designing responsive layouts for the web,
建立一个合理灵活并符合常见设备规格的布局。
build your layouts to be reasonably flexible or within a common device size.
你可以为不同尺寸的设备提供不同布局
Then you can set break points, providing alternative layouts for
这样一来，
those various sizes. Think about it this way,
小屏手机，大屏手机，平板电脑，大型平板电脑就都可以使用了。
small phone, large phone, medium tablet, and large tablet.